{
    "id": "ee2aebcce13545c6b8d69ed214ed479a",
    "title": "Adjective Or Adverb Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have been having a lot of meetings …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "late",
                "lately"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is an ……………………… actor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "excellent",
                "excellently"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He should be able to do it ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "easy",
                "easily"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Take it ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "easy",
                "easily"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is really lazy and ………………… does anything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Alan was very ………………… of the plan.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "critical",
                "critically"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ................................. ill.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "terminal",
                "terminally"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… agree with you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "entire",
                "entirely"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It was a ……………………… waste of time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "complete",
                "completely"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You have ……………………… messed things up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "complete",
                "completely"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}